# **Andrew Tran**



andrewtran1023@live.com



https://trandrew1023.github.io/me



515-657-0589

#### **Education**

**Iowa State University** 

Ames, Iowa

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering
Fall 2016 - Spring 2020 GPA 3.88/4.00

## **Work Experience**

**Cerner Corporation** 

Kansas City, Missouri

Software Engineer I

July 2020 - Present

 Support and develop clinical inventory management (supply chain) applications.

### **Cerner Corporation**

Kansas City, Missouri

Software Intern

May 2019 - August 2019

 Implemented and unit tested part of a web service for message routing using Java.

### **Iowa State University**

Ames, Iowa

Electronics and Technology Group Assistant November 2018 - May 2020

- ETG is the Computer/Electric/Software Engineering's resource for classes, research, and labs.
- Provided equipment and guidance for classes.
- Managed and rebuilt department computers and equipment.
- Managed and recruited for the lab monitoring team.

### **Projects**

#### **aCOUPlefarms**

- Web application to manage a chicken coop (or a couple).
- Users are able to join or create new organizations (ex. farm) with different facilities (ex. coops) to store and view information.
- → React (Material UI components)
- → Axios
- → Spring Boot
- → Postgres/h2

#### **SprintHub**

- Web application created during ShipIt (Cerner hackathon).
- Integrates Jira with story pointing.
- Users are able to host or join a session to view, discuss, and estimate the team's stories/tasks in the same application.
- → React (Material UI components)
- → Express/Axios
- → Firebase (Realtime Database)

### **Economic Home Security System**

- Web application focused on being an affordable home security solution.
- Reduces e-waste by turning cell phones into security cameras.
- → React
- → Django
- → Djoser/SimpleJWT
- → TensorFlow
- → MySQL

#### **That Card**

- Application to help users decide which credit card to use to maximize rewards.
- Project is in the idea/design phase.

#### **Technical Skills**

#### **Languages With Most Experience:**

- Java
- SQL

#### **Languages With Some Experience**:

- Javascript
- HTML/CSS

#### Languages I've Used:

- CCL (Cerner Command Language)
- (
- C#
- Python

#### Tools/Technologies I've Used:

- Android
- Django
- Docker
- Git
- Hadoop
- JBehave
- Jira
- JUnit
- MapReduce
- Maven
- Oracle Database
- Postgres
- React
- Spring

# **Summary**

I enjoy gaining domain and technical knowledge to solve problems. At Cerner, I've worked on a project that prints shelf labels for clinical items, helped build out a new application to search for and manage inventory items, and worked on defects and client tickets that improve user experience.

From learning technical skills like debugging and unit/integration tests to domain knowledge like drug NDCs, barcodes, and EDI, I am excited to keep learning and solve problems.